Guide to the Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, Records SC0650
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-082
  - Community Colleges (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Conferences 1973 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Conferences 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Conferences 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Racism and Law Enforcement Conference (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Wright Institute – Conference of College Presidents (1969) (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Third World Caucus: Stanford University 1970 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Consultants (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Colleges and Universities (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Community Colleges (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Coordinating Council on Higher Education (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Course Descriptions 1970-74 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Cowell Health Center (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Crank letters (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Cultural Events, 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - School of Education Meetings (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Draft Resistance: Chicanos (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Disability Insurance 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Farm Labor Relations Legislation 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Huelga 1969-72 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - United Farmworkers Organizing Committee 1971-73 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Film Festival 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Outlines and Texts (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lists and Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aid 1972-74 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fund Raising: Minority Programs, 1969-73 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Secretary's Office (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Survey for Human Relations Subcommittee 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights Commission 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Internships (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Stanford in Sacramento (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Stanford in Washington 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Programs - KZSU (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lackeys – Administration softball team, 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Latin American Studies Association – Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Latin American Studies (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Law: Chargin, Gerald S. (Judge) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Law: California Rural Legal Assistance (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Law: Centro de Aldeas (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Law: Council on Legal Education Opportunities (CLEO) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Law: Legal Action Matters (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Law: Mexican American Bar Association (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Law: Mexican American Legal Defense (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Law: MALDEF (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Law: Stanford Law School, 1968-74 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Law: Law Students Demands 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Law: California Chicano Law Students Association 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Law: Inquisition – the Death of Baltazar Ordaz Amezcua [court transcript] 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Mexican Government (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Meeting – Faculty (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Fund (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - MECHA, 1971-74 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - East Palo Alto Tutoring Project (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Lettuce Boycott (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bulletins and Catalogs (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mexican-American Cultural Foundation (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Collections and Exhibits (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Assistant Dean of Graduate Studies 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - White House Fellows 1972 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Urban Coalition (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Urban Coalition Information (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Urban/Rural School Development Program (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Urban Studies - Stanford University, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Urban Center: Columbia University 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Youth Opportunity Program 1969-73 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Minorities in Universities and Colleges (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Directives: Stanford University 1974 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Minority Economic Development (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Minority Affairs Committee 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Minority Contractors (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Minority Admission and Recruitment 1969-73 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Mission Coalition Organization (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Modern Language Association of America (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - National Education Task Force for La Raza: Information (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - National Education Task Force for La Raza: Proposals (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - National Education Task Force for La Raza: Reports (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Chicano Pos-Doctoral Fellowships (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Press Releases (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Information (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - News Clippings and Releases: National Information Center on Volunteers in Courts (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - News Clippings and Releases: National Labor Relations Board (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - News Clippings and Releases: Negotiations with Stanford (Minorities) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Various California Publications (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Out-of-state Publications (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - News Releases (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Imperial Valley Publications (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Palo Alto Publications (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Stanford University Publications (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Nostros Unidos (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Nostros Unidos (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Office Machines (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Office of Youth and Student Affairs (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Openings and Replacements (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Openings and Replacements: Hiring Procedures for Assistant Dean of Admissions (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cinco Años: 5 Years of a Community Helping Itself (OIC-CET) ca. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Center/Centro de Entrenamiento para Trabajo (OIC-CET) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Programs: Overseas Programs 1969-74 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Programs: Communications – Colleges and Universities with Minority Programs (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Programs: KZSU (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Programs: Mountain View Teen Post (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Programs: Neighborhood Youth Corps. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Programs: Tutoring-Pilot Program (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Programs: Staff Benefit Programs (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Programs: Summer Upward Bound Program (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - President's Office 1969-74 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - President's and Provost's Office 1970-74 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Community Projects (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Projects: Chicanismo (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Projects: Bakersfield Radio Project (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Projects: Chicano Press at Stanford University (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Projects: Mountain View Tutoring Project (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Pinto Community Center (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Post Doctoral Fellowship Chicano Studies (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Protection of Privacy of Information Report (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Public Health – Chicano Community (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Public Relations (Chicanos) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Publications - Chicano (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Publishers and Publications: La Causa Distribution Center (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Publishers and Publications: Quinto Sol Publications (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Publishers and Publications: Librería Madero (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore ("Keep Up Fight for Americanism") (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Research – Student – Initiated at Graduate Level (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - School of Education: School of Education (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - School of Education: School of Education (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - School of Education: Senate Election (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - School of Education: Graduate Students' Project (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - School of Education: Administrative Scholarships (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Scholarships: College Entrance Examination Board (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Scholarships: Scholarships (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Scholarships: Spain (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Scholarships: Law School (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Scholarships: United Scholarship Service (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Scholarships: Robert Kennedy Memorial Fellowship (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Search Committee – Other Schools (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Senate Committee [CA] on Education 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Student Organizations - Stanford University (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Sun Fund (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Seminars on Bilingualism and Chicano Studies in Mexico City U.C.S.B. 1971-72 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Stanford University [Trustees] Agenda 1969 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Health Insurance - Stanford University (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Speaking Engagements [Luis Nogales] 1969-71 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Stanford University Hospital (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Soledad [Teaching] Project 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Strike: Stanford 1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Study of Between Quarter Temporary Attrition (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Assistanceship at Stanford University (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Educational Teaching Services 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - University Cars (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - University Committee on Minority Affairs 1971-72 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Zoot Suit [film review] 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-210
  General note
  There is no Box 1, 2, 3, or 17 in this accession.
  - Chicano fellows program
    - Trabajadores Culturales (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Union de Artistas/Escritores Chicanos (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Chicano Fellows Evaluation Committee (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Chicano Fellows Evaluation 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Chicano Fellows Evaluation 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chicano Fellows Evaluation 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chicano Orientation 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chicano Fellows Meeting Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Conferencia Sobre La Chicana 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Cinco de Mayo Kermess 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Chicano History Film Series (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Huelga School Community Education Project (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Ignacio Lutero Lopez Exhibit 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Raza Alternative Summer High School 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Chicano Fellows Applications 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Chicano Fellows Evaluation 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Chicano Fellows Meeting Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Chicano Fellows Program Courses (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Chicano Fellows Selection Committee 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Chicano Fellows Meeting Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - ATISBOS Journal of Chicano Research 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - ATISBOS: Frank Garcia 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - ATISBOS: Funding Proposal 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Chicano Colloquium 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Committee in Charge Minutes 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Fellows Program Retreat 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Chicano Fellows Meeting Minutes 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Chicano Fellows Goals and Objectives 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Chicano Fellow Carlos Manuel Chavez (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Chic Ref Library (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Chic Research Fellow Program 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Chicano Fellows Course Descriptions 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Chicano Fellows Meeting Minutes 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Student Leader Contacts 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Chicano Fellows Program Structure 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Chicano Fellows Program File 1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Chicano Fellows Program 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Undergraduate Studies on Chicano Society and Culture 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - CASINDIO Cinco de Mayo 1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Chicano Fellows Staff 1986 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Fernando Gamboa Interview 1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Spring Quarter Schedule 1987 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Amado Padilla Course Syllabus 1987 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Frank Garcia Jr. Course Syllabus 1987 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Robert DeVillar Course Syllabus 1987 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - El Centro Chicano Staff
    - Staff Job Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Maintenance Assignments (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Centro Staff 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Staff Photographs (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Job Announcements and Applications (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Centro Staff (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Staff Retreat 1988 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Centro Staff Positions and Announcements (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Guiding Concilio
    - Collins, J. And Porras, J. Organizational Vision and Visionary Organizations 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Guiding Concilio Meeting #26 4/6/92 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg #27 4/29/92 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #28 5/11/92 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #29 5/29/92 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Guiding Concilio Undergraduate Nominations Information Packet 10/91 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Students Nominations to Guiding Concilio 5/92 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate Students Nominations to Guiding Concilio 5/92 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #23 1/27/92 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Budget (FM) El Centro Chicano 1991-92/Community Meeting, Nov. 19, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Budget Reductions 1991-92/Town Mtg. 10/3/91 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - MJ Letter Conference Room 12/11/91 / 2nd Letter and MJ Response on 12/11 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Letter to MJ 10/25/91 / Response from MJ l 1/14/91 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - MJ Letter (2nd) 12/5/91 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - FM-By Laws 1991-92/Guiding Concilio (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Certificates-Interim Advisory Committee 2/1/91 and Guiding Concilio 5/92 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Ray Bacchetti 1991-91/Meetings-Office of Chicano Affairs (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ray Bacchetti 1991 Office of Chicano Affairs (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Letter to F. De Necochea 7/17/91 Regret from Guiding Concilio (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - F de N 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #25 2/24/92 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Guiding Concilio Staff Nominations 199-91 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. 2/10/92 12:00-1:30 #24 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Guiding Concilio Roster 1990-91 1991-92 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - A Framework for Setting Corporate Vision Draft 1/31/91 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Guiding Concilio Awards SNAP Checks 2/92 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Guiding Concilio Letters $15,000 Award Letters 1/27/92 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Proposals-Guiding Concilio 1/15/92 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Frances Morales Guiding Concilio Proposals (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Letter (by Guiding Concilio) 10/91 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Announcement of 15,000 11/91 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Stanford Si Se Puede Program 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Budget Notes 5/91 Si Se Puede (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Mexican American Affairs Project (Memo to Ray Bacchetti) 3/21/91 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Guiding Concilio 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Jose Chavez mtg 7/18/91 Si Se Puede (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - 5/24/90 Community Meeting RF Packet (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Si Se Puede-Proposed 6/24/91 Funding Letter to J. Chavez (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - El Centro Chicano-Guiding Concilio List 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Policies 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Re-Name Conference Room 6/91 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Guiding Concilio 5/14/91 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #22 1/13/92 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #21 11/22/91 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #20 11/8/91 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #19 1:30-2:30 10/25/91 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #18 1:30-2:30 10/11/91 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #17 9/18/91 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #16 8/23/91 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #15 7/23/91 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #14 7/11/91 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #13 6/18/91 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Sub-Committee Meeting Guiding Concilio 5/30/91 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Guiding Concilio #12 5/28/91 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #11 5/21/91 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Purpose Statement 6/7/91 El Centro Chicano (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #10 5/14/91 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - CGSA Ben Olguin & Esteban burhcard (Leer) 5/14/91 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #9 5/7/91 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg. #8 4/30/91 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Guiding Concilio Mtg Minutes #7 4/23/91 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Guiding Concilio #6 4/12/91 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Guiding Concilio Minutes #5 3/21/91 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Guiding Concilio Minutes #4 3/4/91 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Guiding Concilio Roster 1991 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Guiding Concilio Meeting 6/7/91 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Guiding Concilio 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence 1990-91 Guiding Concilio (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Guiding Concilio Minutes #3 2/25/91 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Guiding Concilio Meeting #2 2/4/91 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Guiding Concilio Meeting #1 1/15/91 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - La Raza Staff- Guiding Concilio 12/90 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Finally! A Framework For Setting Corporate Vision J.C. Collins and JJ Porras 1/13/91 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Minutes 2/4/91 Guiding Concilio #2 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Guiding Concilio 1/15/91 (FM) (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Candidates Night Flyer El Guiding Concilio 10/18/90 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - 5/24/90 Community Meeting Flyer (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - CLOC 1991 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - El Centro Chicano governance 1989-90 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - BCSC Policy Board/Services (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Interim Advisory Committee Members 7/8/90 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 10/10/90 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 9/24/90 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Guiding Concilio Faculty Member 11/90 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 6/22/90 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Minutes 6/22/90 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Int. Adv. Com-Mtg 5/29/90 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Interim Advisory Committee Minutes 5/29/90 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Guiding Concilio Drafts 5/90 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Proposal Guiding Concilio 3/24/90 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Int. Adv. Com. 5/24/90 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Int. Advisory Com. 5/8/90 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - 5/24/90 community Mtg. Mail out (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Interim Advisory Committee Minutes 5/29/90 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Community Mtgs. Agenda Flyer 5/24/90 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - FM Folder Interim Advisory Committee 1990 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Questionnaires Received 1990 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Interim Governance 1990 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 4/25/90 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Interim Advisory Committee 4/4/90 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Minutes 3/19/90 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Meeting 3/5/90 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Agenda 2/16/90 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Minutes 2/9/90 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Agenda 2/8/90 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Minutes 2/8/90 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - El Centro Affiliated Organizations, 1990-1992
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The National Hispanic Institute (Fellows Program), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Student Staff Announcement, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Coordinator Positions (Applicants), 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Staff Applications, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - SU Temporary Agency, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Financial Aids Office: Student Employment, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - BA Coordinator Job Listings, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - El Centro Chicano Coordinators, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Early Arrival Housing Info: (Roberto Almanzan & Delia Lopez), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Federal Work Study, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Student Employment Federal Listings, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Staff Job Announcements, 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Work Study, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - FM Applications - Staff, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Staff Interview Questions, 33150 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - El Centro Student Staff Applicants, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Staff Job Announcements, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Coordinator Positions Applications, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Aurora-Fisher-Buck, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Youth Opportunity Program (Alex Arredondo), 33025 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - A.A.A.C. Program Coordinator Position, 33451 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - El Centro Office Manager Applicants, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - El Centro Office Manager (Applications), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Screening Criteria for Office Manager Position, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - El Centro Office Manager Announcement, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Personnel, 1984-1985
    - David Ayon, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - George A. Cuevas, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Alonso Duenos, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Deanna Flores, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Georgina Hernandez, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Augie Rivera, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Alice Stauffer, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Dorian Woods, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Personnel, 1983-1984
    - Dave Campa, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Carlos Castellanos, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Emilio Cruz, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Alonso Duenas, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Kim Fairbanks, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Chris Flores, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Deanna Flores, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Amparo (Mary) Garcia, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Leti Marquez, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Sharon Padilla, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - David Moguel, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Cynthia Parral, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Lisa Parral, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Ed Romero, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Arturo Vargas, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Sandra Viera, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Dorian Woods, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Organization costs, 1980-1992
    - Academic Organizations Board (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - C.O.S.S. Charge for 1979 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Budgets, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Budgets, 1992-93 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Chicano Cultural Center, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - La ONDA Telephone Bills, 1980-81 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - El Centro Forms
    - SSP Forms (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Employment Eligibility Verification (Form I-9) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stanford University Payroll/Personnel Action Forms, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - FORMS: El Centro Student Staff Weekly Schedule, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - SU 32 - Employee's Tax Data, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Accounting Forms
    - Budget Projection Forms (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Deposit Forms (Transmittal of Departmental Collections) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Authorization for Electronic Real Access (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Event Evaluation Form: El Centro Chicano, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Forms
    - Interdepartmental Request (SU - 13) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Organizational Contact List (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Univ. Events Services (PE -100) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Operating Budget Fund Transfers Forms (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Bookstore Requisitions (SU 12) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - University Map - Bechtel Highlighted (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Maps (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Workers' Compensation (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Centro Chicano Original Forms (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - General Information & Procedures (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Tresidder Request Forms (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Employment Packet (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Events and Issues, 1990-1992
    - CORE Mtgs, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Cowell Student Health Center, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - SU Chicano Alumni, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)